{
    "id": "d4e1726b615b4326816309fedac3277e",
    "title": "Exercise: Grammar check",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f1ee140975b7414e876905edc2b2335d",
            "title": "Grammar Check",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Words used to modify nouns are called …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "adverb",
                        "adjective",
                        "preposition"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Adverbs can modify verbs, adjectives and other adverbs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The present perfect tense can be used with past time adverbs like yesterday and last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In the simple present tense, we use did to make questions and negatives.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The present continuous tense can be used to talk about future events.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Modal auxiliaries do not have infinitives or –ing forms.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We cannot use the article a/an with uncountable nouns.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When enough modifies a noun, it goes after it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We need two conjunctions to join two clauses.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Prepositions can go at the end of a sentence.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Proper nouns always begin with a capital letter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "True",
                        "False"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following can be used to join two clauses?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Conjunctions",
                        "Relative pronouns",
                        "Relative adverbs",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}